(Hot Debut)
(Hyun Moo has something on his face.)
- What's that? - What's that?
- What's he doing? - My gosh.
- It matches the wall too. - What is that?
- Right. - Is he the Tin Man?
- What's wrong with you? - It's about time he ironed out...
- his face. - It was an important day.
So I wore the strongest facial sheet that day.
You look like a sweet potato in my oven.
- A sweet potato in your oven. - Gosh, this...
- He's wrapped in tinfoil. - A wrapped sweet potato.
- You didn't waste two seconds... - The inside color matches...
- to mock me. - that of a sweet potato too.
From afar, it looks like you'd be in "Descent of Warriors."
"Descent of Warriors?" That's so funny.
He kind of matches the song, "Descent of Warriors."
- "High-five of the 40s." - The song is playing.
It's so crowded on the street.
People must have thought, "He's doing performance art."
- Like the guy in Paris. - Right.
- They don't move at first, but... - A performance artist.
- they do when you try to film them. - They move then.
Right.
- Come on. Seriously. - They kick their hat to put it on.
(Come on. Stop teasing me.)
(He's quite the spectacle.)
(Glancing around)
- What? - What's going on with him?
(He's just standing still while sneaking glances at people.)
- Yes. Why are you glancing at them? - He's at the most crowded section.
(Is that Kian84 walking toward him from a distance?)
Hyun Moo.
You startled me.
What's that on your face?
- A facial sheet. - What?
I always put on a facial sheet before going to the salon.
- I do that. - You should.
I've never seen anyone wearing that on the street, though.
Does it come with the jacket?
- No. I bought this separately. - It matches your jacket.
Who would wear a matching jacket with the facial sheet?
- Who would do that? - Your jacket matches...
- the facial sheet. - This is good for my face.
I also tried another facial sheet the night before.
It was the one Lingard wore. The PDRN facial sheet.
- Okay. - I wore two of them before bed.
- Good job. - Good job.
Gosh, I'm a bit nervous.
Why are you nervous?
Jang Woo told me you were nervous.
- Being an MC at a wedding... - But...
isn't that hard.
But this is my first time.
No, being an MC at a wedding is nervous.
- It really is. - My goodness.
This is my first time officiating a wedding too.
Jang Woo is finally getting married today.
On his wedding day, Kian84 and I are making a hot debut.
Kian84 will be the MC, and I will be the wedding officiant.
Hyun Moo.
- Na Rae. - That was our trip to Turkiye.
- It feels like a long time ago. - Oh, my.
- I teared up that day. - Jang Woo, the crybaby.
This is my last trip with you.
(The Palm Oil Family's last trip ended in tears.)
- Hey. - Gosh, he's married now.
(Jang Woo stopped crying and said something.)
(He asked Hyun Moo, a bachelor, to officiate his wedding.)
- It was moving. Then I was shocked. - What's going on?
(Kian84 was chosen to be the MC at the wedding.)
(Feeling reassured)
So we need to look better than we've ever looked in our lives.
- Of course. - I invited Kian84...
to my beauty salon.
- You went to the professionals. - Jang Woo texted me...
- past midnight. - Right.
Hello.
Your jacket matches the facial sheet.
Oh, this? That wasn't my intention, though.
(Feeling awkward)
You can remove it.
- You're officiating the wedding? - Yes.
- I'm officiating the wedding. - You are?
- Are you the MC then? - Yes.
He's the MC at the wedding.
- There's a hairstyle for MCs. - Make him look neat.
Then could you trim my sideburns...
- and the back hair? - Just trim them a bit?
- And just make my hair look good. - That's good.
Make it look nice and round.
- Give him a neat hairstyle. - My hair tends to spike up.
- Make it round. - Okay.
Just because I'm officiating the wedding,
don't make me look so serious.
Don't make me look old. Make me look young, actually.
Like the wedding officiant for the zoomers.
- Okay. - I want my skin to look bright.
The cotton pads get stuck on your facial hair.
Pieces of them get ripped by my facial hair.
That rarely happens.
(They're getting their makeup done.)
(Hyun Moo is focused on something.)
Gosh, this is crazy. I can't focus at all.
It was my first time officiating a wedding,
so I didn't know the proper length.
You were busy, but you wrote out the speech.
That's dense.
- I wrote 2 whole A4 pages. - My gosh.
(He keeps reading the speech while getting his makeup done.)
(Kian84 is also getting his makeup done.)
(They're dolled up as the wedding officiant and MC.)
- You're good. That's it. - Thank you.
(Someone walks down in a fancy outfit.)
I just decided to wear a suit that made me look young.
It as the perfect example of a dandy look.
(Winking)
(Korea's first unmarried wedding officiant look)
I'm the wedding officiant for the zoomers.
He tried to sound young.
Wait. But you did dress up like a traditional officiant.
- No. I looked young that day. - On the wedding day?
I thought you were trying...
- to look old on purpose. - You looked quite serious.
Why would I try to look old on purpose?
You looked like a character...
- from "The Divine Move." - Right.
You looked like the go player in the movie.
- Really? - You were officiating the wedding.
You would've looked really nice...
- if the suit was a bit tighter. - That would've been better?
Hyun Moo. Even if you did, they would've teased you again.
Why do you keep asking them?
- What do you want me to do? - They would've teased you anyway.
They would've said I was too much.
- We would've said to iron it. - Come on.
I'm the wedding officiant for the zoomers.
(No matter what they say, I'm the officiant for the zoomers.)
(A gentleman is dressed in a sharp suit.)
- This is... - My gosh. Who's this now?
- Kian84 looks great in suits. - My gosh.
My gosh, Kian84. You could go up...
- against Park Jeong Min. - It suits him.
Let's go!
- Don't say that. - My gosh.
- But you did look great that day. - Right.
Your hair and makeup looked great.
He's tall...
- and has a good body proportion. - Right.
- Of course. - With the hair and makeup done,
- he looked normal. - People around me said that too.
- "Normal?" - The ladies said that...
you looked so handsome.
- Right. - I heard all of that too.
It felt great hearing that I looked handsome.
It's on me.
- What? - It's on me.
(The wedding officiant pays for their makeovers.)
- Thank you, Hyun Moo. - Sure.
Let me pay for the cab.
I already called one.
My gosh.
- Hello. - Hello.
You're always treating me.
(Writing something down)
What are you writing down?
"Height, 184cm. Weight, 108kg."
- The groom's introduction? - Yes. "Groom Lee Jang Woo, enter."
When he's walking down the aisle,
shouldn't I say something? When he walks down...
I say a few comments when grooms walk down for a reason.
This is their first time too, so they feel awkward.
"Walk down confidently." I say things like that.
"You're the man of the hour." I try to help them relax.
But it's not mandatory or anything.
(Taking notes right away)
And when the wedding aisle is long,
people stop clapping halfway through.
It's hard to keep on clapping.
"Please give a big round of applause and cheer for the groom."
Then they start clapping loudly.
Say things like that.
- Hyun Moo helped you a lot. - Yes.
- "The lady of the hour." - Yes.
But how come the brides get all the attention at the weddings?
Shouldn't grooms be in the center of attention too?
It's the day they look the prettiest.
Don't you know the term, SDM?
They've been taking care of themselves...
- to look the best at weddings. - Right.
It's like a big reveal to the guests.
- People call it SDM? - SDM.
Like the Japanese anime movie?
- "Suzume." - That's...
- That's "Suzume." - "SDM?"
You...
(The movie is called "Suzume.")
Why would you mention the movie? They're completely different.
Hyun Moo. How should I handle this?
"Please give them an even bigger round of applause..."
"than when they walked in."
- "Please bless their future." - Right.
That's such a useful tip.
When the couple kisses, tell them...
they'll start with the family and friends photo.
That's the most important.
There are things you don't need to say.
- Don't say those things. - Don't?
If you're not sure, don't say it.
By the way,
if I get too nervous, could you take over?
I mean it.
(The expert wedding MC everyone can rely on)
I've been an MC at so many weddings since I became an announcer.
- I'm sure Dae Ho can relate. - Yes.
I must've attended 1,000 weddings.
Up until recently, I went to 5 weddings in 1 month as the MC.
When I'm asked to be a wedding MC, I don't get nervous at all.
I just go to the wedding and do my things.
I even do it without a script.
Hyun Moo has done it a lot.
I can do it with my eyes closed.
Hyun Moo, you can write a book on how to be an MC at weddings.
"The Perfect Wedding MC."
("The Perfect Wedding MC")
(Being an MC at weddings? You can totally nail it now.)
(By Writer Jun Hyun Moo)
What is this?
He must've done...
- all kinds of weddings. - Of course.
- You can run an academy. - Outdoors and indoors.
I've been an MC at every kind of wedding.
All kinds of weddings.
It feels so reliable to have you.
(What's the point? He's a newbie officiant today.)
(His lips are dry.)
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
What tone should I use for my speech?
(Swallowing hard)
He's starting to get nervous now.
(They're getting close to the wedding venue.)
(The closer they get to the venue, the more nervous they become.)
My gosh, this is killing me.
(This is my first time officiating the wedding.)
Oh, no.
(I can do a good job, right?)
"All right. The bride and groom will enter now."
(A few minutes ago, the car was filled with laughter.)
- You were laughing before. - Oh, no.
My gosh. I know how that feels.
But still. Both of them won the Grand Award.
- They come with impressive resumes. - We're both newbies at weddings.
- Right. - Yes.
I hadn't been that nervous in a while.
Oh, no. I'm getting nervous too.
(The newbie officiant is nervous as he's about to debut.)
There are so many people.
Of course.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(They quickly arrive at the venue before they can brace themselves.)
- You look so handsome. - Hello.
They look so handsome.
Hello.
Which floor is it?
You can go to the second floor.
Gosh, there are so many people.
Oh, my. There are so many people.
(Bustling)
(Welcome to Jang Woo and Hye Won's wedding.)
- That's Hye Won. - They look so good together.
- The wedding hall was stunning too. - Gosh, how grand.
(The wedding hall was as grand as Jang Woo.)
Half of them were actors. The other half were chefs.
All the chefs I saw on TV came to his wedding.
(Surrounded by a large crowd of guests...)
There's Jang Woo!
(the groom, Jang Woo, is taking photos with his parents.)
Look at him. He's nervous.
(His cherished friends have gathered for Jang Woo.)
- They were on our show before. - Oh, it's those guys.
(Ha Jae Suk, Lee Jun Haeng)
Ha Jae Suk.
(Jung Ji Sun, Im Tae Hoon)
- Right. - Self-Made Chef.
(John Park, Yoon Si Yoon)
A lot of actors and actresses came too.
It's like watching a drama.
It's like watching "Jang Bori is Here."
"Jang Bori is Here."
(Laughing)
- Jang Woo. You're so busy. - You must be busy.
- Okay. - I'm the officiant.
(They finally meet the man of the hour today.)
- All right. - You should wear the boutonniere.
- The boutonniere. - Over here.
Wait, wear the boutonniere.
Please put it on me.
- I didn't know you had to wear one. - It's for the MC and officiant.
- Look at the camera. One, two. - Hello.
- One, two. - Hello.
Why does Kian84 look so awkward?
There's the facial expression he makes when he's nervous.
Do a cool pose. One, two.
Let's go.
- Okay. Thank you. - Thank you.
- We'll go and get ready. - Yes.
- You're the MC at this wedding. - Yes, Hyun Moo.
(The wedding MC and officiant finally enter the wedding hall.)
- Hello. - Hello.
This is the podium for the MC.
Where's the podium for the officiant?
- Is there a table for me? - Yes, there is.
(Where's my table?)
He's going in.
It's just getting started now.
You put it here?
(A cute and cozy table for Moomoo)
(It's in a small corner of this spacious wedding hall.)
It looks like a tarot card reading stall.
You look like an adult straight up sitting in that corner.
- Oh, my. Goodness. - Yes.
I see.
Gosh, I can't believe I'm doing this.
(The officiant's signature will certify their marriage.)
If I don't sign this, the wedding will be invalid, right?
(Jang Woo needs to get married.)
Okay.
He's the witness to their marriage.
- I'll put it on the podium. - Okay.
This is driving me crazy. Now that I'm here,
I'm getting nervous. My gosh.
My back was getting sweaty.
(He nervously reviews his speech.)
(Locked away in his solitary corner,)
(he focuses on reviewing the speech.)
(Grabbing)
(Downing a sip)
(Downing two sips)
He drank up the whole glass.
Then you'll want to go to the restroom.
I suddenly want to pee.
- Gosh. - See?
I guess I was nervous.
It's been a while since I saw you get this nervous.
(This guy can't stop drinking water either.)
- We did drink a lot of water. - Yes.
(Let me see.)
(MC84 keeps on reviewing the program nonstop.)
What is it?
"The groom will enter now."
My gosh. I'd be scared at that moment too.
When you do anything for the first time,
- you get nervous. - When I was next to him...
It's nerve-racking because it affects his life.
- Right. - Yes.
And the parents of the bride and groom...
only rely on us.
- Right. - That's true.
- No one can help us. - Right.
And there's so much you have to check as the MC.
I thought it wasn't a big job.
But MCs have to check the lighting too.
- Of course. - There are many things...
- they must check the timing for. - Right.
Do you know when the most nerve-racking moment is?
Five or ten minutes before the ceremony,
they make announcements.
- I start to get nervous then. - "Dear guests."
- "Soon, we will begin..." - Yes.
- That makes me nervous. - That announcement?
(Will I be able to do a good job?)
(Turning around)
(Sinking his head)
(Dear Buddha...)
I prayed to Buddha.
So I wouldn't make mistakes.
- This is a piece of cake. - Okay, Hyun Moo.
- Let's do this. - Okay.
And if there's something wrong, give me a signal.
- Or call my name. - Hyun Moo.
Great.
- I'm glad that... - Seriously.
you guys had each other.
Right. You guys relied on each other a lot.
- Of course. - Yes.
In the ten years I've known you guys,
you've never looked closer.
- They look like besties. - Right.
- You always criticized each other. - Yes.
- I got nervous when you went in. - Really?
Having you by my side helped a lot. I relied on you.
(They have bonded over deeply over this nervous moment.)
(Hyun Moo goes back to the solitary corner.)
To the solitary corner.
(Looking cozy)
- Let's go over the script together. - Hello.
- Would you mind? - No.
Please make the announcement at 6pm and 6:05pm...
that the ceremony will start soon.
- In 5 and 10 minutes? - Yes.
I'll stay next to you and remind you.
Okay.
And exactly at 6:10pm,
announce that the wedding will begin.
Then you can start the program.
- Then you can start the program. - Kian84.
Is everything okay?
I'll tell you later.
He wants you to stay in the corner.
"Stay inside, old man."
Gosh, I should help Kian84.
(The old man is worried.)
(Walking up)
- This is your corner? - Yes.
I see. This is your corner.
You don't seem as nervous as before.
No.
You can do this. It's not that hard.
This is nice, right? It's like the Entertainment Awards.
Sure.
(Contrary to what he said, he doesn't look okay.)
- My gosh. - I was spacing out too.
(Are we going to be able to pull this off?)
- There were so many people. - Right.
My gosh. This place is nice.
(A table prepared just for the Rainbow Club members)
You were the first one to arrive.
I was the first one.
(The Rainbow Club members arrive one at a time.)
Check the menu. The meal looks great.
CODE KUNST.
Hey, Kang Yong.
Hello.
- Everyone came in order. - Hey.
- Gosh, you're here. - I'm glad to see you. Hey.
It's nice to meet everyone...
after the field day.
Right.
Have you been well?
How are things these days?
I've been working hard at my job.
(Oh, my)
We've all become close.
- Thanks to the field day. - Yes.
By the way, KEY can't make it.
- KEY is overseas for work. - Right.
- I should've been there too. - Right.
You know what? Jang Woo...
He must've been good to people.
Look at the hall. It's packed.
(10 minutes before the ceremony begins)
You can check the microphone if it's working well...
by making the first announcement that the ceremony will begin soon.
- Right. It's starting. - Here it goes. He's going to talk.
- Should I begin? - Yes.
- Gosh. - Great.
All right.
- All right. - Right.
We will soon begin...
- Right. Kian84... - He's here.
- He's the MC. - He's here.
(Gosh, it's Kian84.)
Groom Lee Jang Woo and Bride Jo Hye Won's...
wedding ceremony.
Dear guests,
please take your seat and sit down.
"Take your seat and sit down?" What's he saying?
He's nervous.
I wanted them to sit properly.
Please put your phone on vibrate.
We'll begin shortly.
- I kept it casual at the end. - Great.
That was great, by the way.
The unique tone of your voice gets people's attention.
- Really? - Yes. It's nice and refreshing.
(He finishes his first announcement in a charming way.)
- You can keep that tone. - Okay.
Great job.
(I just finished my first task.)
(Sighing)
(You can do this, Kian84.)
Wait. Are you the great-great grandpa?
- What is this? - Hold on.
Are you the mountain spirit or what?
He looks like a dethroned king too.
What is this?
He looks like a king who got exiled to a tiny shack.
- Right. - He looks like a greedy king.
That fancy suit looks like the white ramie outfit.
Seriously. It looks like he just lost all of his power.
He looks like someone secretly living at the wedding hall.
A dethroned king.
(The dethroned king, King Moomoo, is secretly living in the hall.)
(The ceremony is about to begin now.)
(The newbie officiant and MC are making final preparations.)
(Utterly nervous)
My expectations are suddenly going up.
(MC84 picks up the microphone with determination.)
Shall we begin? Okay.
(I'm watching you.)
"Who plotted treason?"
"I need to get my throne back."
Dear guests, it's nice to meet you all.
I am...
(Cheering)
He likes that.
(The guests give him a big round of applause.)
(You're so cool, Kian84!)
Okay.
(Screaming)
That was great.
(He must be so excited.)
All right. I'm the MC of today's wedding.
My name is Kian84.
Let's have a great wedding together.
- Great. - Gosh, he did a good job.
He finally looks relaxed.
Great.
I'd like to thank the families, close friends, and acquaintances...
for attending the wedding.
We will now begin Groom Lee Jang Woo...
and Bride Jo Hye Won's wedding ceremony.
Dear guests,
please give them a big round of applause. Okay?
Nice.
(His tone is weirdly charming.)
- "Okay?" - It's like we're at a nightclub.
- "Okay?" - "Okay?"
(He's pretty good.)
To begin today's sacred ceremony,
I would like to introduce...
the officiant.
He's coming out soon.
(The hot debut of the unmarried officiant)
Kian84 has already started.
This is a special guy.
So his introduction is quite long.
- His introduction is long. - I wrote it.
(Of course, it's long.)
In 2017, 2022, and 2024,
he won the Grand Award...
at the MBC Entertainment Awards.
He's been hosting I Live Alone for ten years.
He's become the idol of single men and women in Korea.
- I wrote that. - The idol of single people?
(Let me see.)
He's the captain of the Palm Oil Family,
a group the groom, Lee Jang Woo, is a part of.
He's a mentor to the groom.
- He wrote that himself? - Great.
Yes.
I was going to take this part out, but he insisted that I read it.
(An all-knowing smile)
Now, he's known as Moorathoner.
He's known as Moorathoner.
(Why did he bring up Moorathoner at the wedding?)
That was good. Everyone laughed at that.
- Really? - Yes. See?
I wanted Kian84 to say this.
- Look at his satisfied smile. - Look at him.
He's trying his best to promote...
the stress-free, fun run which is the first in Korea.
Please welcome Mr. Jun Hyun Moo with a round of applause.
Gosh, I keep messing up the lines.
Because you didn't want to say them.
- He didn't mean that. - You were lying.
My tongue kept getting numb.
(The tongue of the truth)
(Yes, it's me. I'm Moorathoner.)
(Brazen)
(Clapping as if they were under a spell)
All right. They're the reason we all showed up today.
We will now invite in the bride and groom.
- Jang Woo will walk in now. - Jang Woo will enter.
- He must be nervous. Oh, my. - Oh, my.
You look good!
(As the guests applaud,)
(the groom is ready to walk down the aisle.)
He looked so dashing.
- Oh, my. - Gosh, I'm nervous.
(I should get ready too.)
The paper is shaking.
Height, 184cm.
It's 185cm.
Weight, 108kg.
- He didn't correct that. - He's been growing...
on public's love as the pop culture artist.
He will no longer live alone.
He will set out on a new journey with his loved one.
The prince of the Palm Oil Family...
always cultivates a new path to face new changes.
Groom Lee Jang Woo.
Enter now.
That was good.
(What? That was nice and neat.)
- That was neat. - Nicely done.
Did you write down the introduction for the groom?
I like martial arts.
- That's the vibe I was going for. - Right.
At UFC fights, they always mention the height.
- Right. - I see.
- Nicely done. It was great. - So...
Groom Lee Jang Woo.
Enter now.
That was pretty good.
(Powerful)
(As MC84 energetically invites him in...)
You look handsome!
Congratulations, Jang Woo!
(The Rainbow Club members are watching him with pride.)
You look handsome!
You look so strong!
(Chuckling)
I liked the soundtrack too.
(Here comes Kung Fu Jang Woo.)
It's the soundtrack to "Kung Fu Panda?"
He chose it himself.
- That song was perfect. - Yes.
(Bravely walking toward his Act 2)
Please give him a big round of applause.
(Seeing Jang Woo with full of confidence...)
The man of the hour is bravely walking down...
the aisle.
(I should take pictures of him.)
(Smiling brightly)
(They laughed over silly things.)
My gosh. Time flew by.
That was quite a long time ago.
- Right. - Yes.
(They've become a family before they knew it.)
(As Jang Woo sets out to make a new family of his own...)
- You look great! - Here's our groom.
(they clap to show support.)
He looks especially grand and handsome today.
He can stand...
shoulder to shoulder with Cha Eun Woo if he loses weight.
(After a witty introduction of the groom...)
Next up is the lady of the hour.
She's the most beautiful bride in the world.
Ms. Jo Hye Won will enter now.
I guess she's coming out from there.
Dear guests, could you turn around to the back?
No, it's over there.
- It's the most anticipated moment. - How lovely.
No one will look as beautiful as the bride today.
(The bride dressed in pure white walks in through the door.)
I wonder how that must have felt.
- It's like a scene from a drama. - Yes.
She looks so beautiful.
(She smiles brightly like a beautiful pile of snow.)
Our stunning bride...
- is walking down. - She looks so beautiful.
Everyone, please give her a big round of applause.
I wonder how Jang Woo felt at this moment.
We would never know.
Gosh, she's tearing up.
Already?
She must be feeling all kinds of emotions.
Right.
Here comes...
the most beautiful bride.
(Walking toward Jang Woo one step at a time)
Here she is.
Gosh, I'm feeling emotional.
I might tear up. Oh, no.
I must be getting hit with female hormones.
What's wrong with me?
He reminded me of this lady I go to dry sauna with.
(Tearing up)
(Breathing on it)
- What are you doing? - Did you take a selfie?
(I ought to capture this moment.)
(I'll include my face too.)
Why are you crying?
(They hold hands and stand in front of Hyun Moo.)
Finally,
our groom and bride...
walked down the aisle confidently and beautifully.
Next, the couple will bow to each other...
in front of the guests...
and their families...
as a gesture of respect.
(The groom and bride turn to face each other.)
(Feeling proud)
- They must bow now. - Tell them to bow.
- Tell them to bow. - Hyun Moo has to say that.
Hyun Moo has to say that.
- I was supposed to say that? - Yes.
The officiant actually says it.
It seems you were the one who needed help.
You had to say that.
- You actually... - Kian84 was more prepared.
- You actually needed more help. - Right.
(They end up bowing at each other on their own.)
Groom. Bride. Bow to each other.
(With his eyes fixed on the script, he failed to see their bow.)
Oh, no. They already did it.
- Will they have to do it? - They can't do it again.
- They did it again? - They did another one?
(Bowing for the 2nd time)
(Hyun Moo, I got you covered.)
(Feeling proud)
(Clapping for the 2nd time)
Next, the wedding vow...
will be read out loud by Officiant Jun Hyun Moo.
Here is the wedding vow.
Groom Lee Jang Woo.
Bride Jo Hye Won.
Do you vow to be faithful...
and honor your duty as husband and wife?
I do.
- Groom. - Yes.
I know how much food you've eaten.
Get your energy up and say it loudly.
- Do you vow to do so? - I do!
Can you guys hear him in the back?
- Yes. - Yes.
Yes, he must say it out loud.
- Officiants often request that. - Do you...
- Bride. - Yes.
- Do you vow to do so? - I do!
(I do!)
- That was amazing! - Hye Won is so cool.
She's a girl crush.
We have now finished the wedding vow.
I now solemnly declare before all of you that...
these two are now joined as husband and wife.
November 23, 2025.
Officiant Jun Hyun Moo.
(You make a cool officiant.)
His pronunciation and vocalization were great.
That's how it is with announcers.
You've got that voice.
- Right. - He was so good.
It was nice and neat.
To bless their future as husband and wife,
the officiant...
- He prepared a lot. - will say a few words...
Gosh, it was amazing how much he prepared for the wedding.
Our respected officiant...
I can hear the mockery in your voice.
(I can hear the mockery in your voice.)
Mr. Jun Hyun Moo will deliver a speech now.
(Inhaling deeply)
It was my first time standing there as an officiant.
It was a sight I had never seen before.
I could see Jang Woo in front of me.
I couldn't see anyone in the back.
- I couldn't see anyone. - Right.
- I could only see the couple. - Yes, from where you're standing.
It was pitch-black in the back.
So I almost thought that it was just...
the three of us up there. That's how it felt.
That must be a nerve-racking moment.
All right. Let me formally introduce myself.
Hello.
Since the establishment of our country,
I'm the first person to be an officiant...
without walking down the aisle myself.
I'm an incredible officiant.
I've been on I Live Alone and known Kian84 for ten years.
My name is Jun Hyun Moo. Nice to meet you all.
- President Jun! - The vibe was nice.
(The guests respond with a round of applause.)
I've been an MC at countless weddings.
But I've never been in a position where I got to look at the couple...
and the guests at the same time.
I'm quite nervous.
So I hope you will show me support with applause.
- I never knew he got nervous too. - Okay?
- Yes! - Okay.
Actually, singing at weddings makes me most nervous too.
- They only have one wedding. - Right.
- Exactly. - Yes.
When Jang Woo asked me...
to be an officiant at his wedding, not the MC,
honestly, I was quite flustered.
To be blunt, I wondered if he was trying to ruin me.
That crossed my mind too.
The 3 of us met 2 days ago.
Here's what he said.
"I want people who are close to me to officiate,"
"act as an MC, and sing at my wedding."
"And I only want to invite people whom I consider special."
That's what he said.
After hearing what he said, I fell for that temptation...
and ended up standing here.
That part was funny.
Please remember that you're a very meaningful guest...
to Lee Jang Woo and Jo Hye Won.
I felt so lost while preparing to officiate the wedding...
that I went to a large bookstore two months ago...
and bought a book titled "A Monk's Wedding Speech."
I read the entire book.
I made preparations to share good words...
and prevent myself from doing a disservice to the wedding.
Although this book is about the wedding speech,
it begins with, "A married couple..."
"must never rely on..."
"or depend on each other."
Isn't it ironic?
Your loved one is often called...
- your other half. - Your other half.
But Monk Pomnyun says this.
"It may appear that two half hearts have made a full heart."
"But that heart is cracked."
"Your spouse isn't your other half."
"When your whole and the other's whole meet..."
"and make a full heart,"
"it's true love."
- He has a way with words. - He really does.
He's the best.
While talking to the two of them,
I filled two pieces of A4 paper.
That was how touched I was.
As I say this,
I'll relay a short message to the two of them.
He hasn't gotten to the point yet, right?
I think that's the introduction.
I think they're beginning to get bored.
There's always someone who can't stay focused.
We aren't used to the officiant's message.
Also, most officiants keep the message short these days.
"Here comes the officiant's message."
"Live well. The end."
- It goes like that. - That's right.
I've just begun.
(Moomoo's message has just begun.)
Although they haven't read the book,
they follow the teachings of Monk Pomnyun.
They don't expect anything from each other...
or rely on each other.
They live their separate lives to the fullest.
They don't ask anything of each other.
They live their lives that way.
He's repeating himself.
(Laughing)
What am I going to do? I'm losing my focus.
It's a challenge for Hyun Moo too. The officiant's message is boring.
(Joking)
When did I say that?
That table is the most distracted.
It's very boring.
Gochujang grilled sole sounds delicious.
Gochujang grilled sole.
- Is this the menu? - Yes.
(They read the wedding menu that's more interesting.)
Lastly, I'll tell you this.
- The last part. - The last part.
It must be the first in Korea.
Upon meeting the two of them,
I've established my belief on marriage.
And I've learned about my ideal type.
Before that,
- I'll also become whole. - I thought that was the last part.
Also, it must be the first since the establishment of Korea.
Kian84 is bored.
Weddings in the early 2000s were like this.
I was reminded of the past.
- "Lastly..." - "Before I end..."
- "Lastly..." - "I'll say one more thing."
- Yes. - "Also..."
"Because of that..."
I've learned about life from these two.
Hye Won said this to me.
You wouldn't know, but Jang Woo said this to me.
I...
So I thought to myself...
Jang Woo said this to me.
"I..."
He talks about himself too much.
Lee Ju Seung, that punk!
We should tell him to stop.
He's acting like it's his own wedding.
Ju Seung, it's his talk show.
It's too much.
- Ju Seung got his revenge then. - While I was gone...
It's a bit like "Sebasi Talk."
Kian84 is touching his tie.
- Kian84 is touching his tie. - "Sebasi Talk."
(Dazed)
Please give a round of applause to Jo Hye Won.
He's hosting.
(He asked people to clap on "Jun Hyun Moo Show.")
"Jun Hyun Moo Show."
With this monk's message,
I'll wrap things up.
The drama where they met for the first time...
was "My Only One."
They've found each other's only one in life.
I sincerely congratulate them.
They say that your life follows the title of the show.
My representative work is I Live Alone.
I'll continue to live alone diligently,
so I hope the two of them will be happy.
- Why did you say that? - Why did you share your thoughts?
That came out of nowhere.
I let people know that I was single.
Lead a cool life respectively.
I'll root for you guys. Thank you.
(He ends the message by telling people that he's single.)
We've listened to the touching message...
- from the officiant. - That's a mockery.
Officiant, please take your leave.
That was funny.
- He spoke for everyone. - Yes.
"Please take your leave."
(Officiant takes his leave.)
(He comes back to his seat after completing his task.)
Well done.
- It was cool. - It was incredible.
I can't believe these two-faced people.
Well done.
- It was touching. - Really?
- Some people cried. - It was no joke.
Who cried?
- Did you cry? - Yes.
Many people cried.
(Did people shed tears?)
If some people cried, my message must've been touching.
And the most crucial review came from Hwang Shin Hye.
She said my wedding message was the most entertaining.
Out of the wedding messages she has heard in her life,
mine was the most entertaining and touching.
Oh, my.
It's my first time seeing you...
- in real life. - It's our first time meeting.
I was so surprised.
I can't believe you came to say hello.
- Thank you. - Today's wedding message...
- Okay. - was the most entertaining one...
- out of the ones I've heard. - Really?
It was Hwang Shin Hye's pick.
That boosted my confidence.
Moomoo's wedding message. The Gen Z wedding message.
It was a success. It was a hot debut.
- A hot debut. - It was so successful...
that I'm afraid people will line up to ask me to be the officiant.
All right.
It was nice.
- Hyun Moo. - You were like a real officiant.
Seriously.
- What? This song? - This song?
Everyone!
- "For the moon, by the sea." - It's Hwanhee.
Jang Woo's cousin, Hwanhee.
I didn't expect to hear that song.
(Feeling relieved, Hyun Moo grooves to the song.)
("Sea of Love" by FLY TO THE SKY)
(Until they dry up)
(Their good cheer won't dry up.)
(Dancing)
(Everyone enjoys the wedding song.)
- Thank you. - Please give him a big hand.
(Clapping)
Groom and bride,
please bow to the parents.
(The wedding is coming to an end.)
Finally, two people who were living alone...
became one...
as a married couple.
So that they can live well...
with wisdom and happiness,
please give them a passionate round of applause.
Groom and bride.
Toward the bright future!
March!
They must be nervous.
(With the host's word, the two of them march.)
My legs would go weak.
Please congratulate them with a round of applause.
- You're cool. - You're cool.
You're pretty.
- Jang Woo, you look handsome. - Congratulations.
- You're pretty. - You're cool.
(Blessings pour in like petals.)
(The two bless the youngest member of Palm Oil Family.)
Oh, no.
(It began from an offhand comment.)
- Where are you going? - What?
- Are you going somewhere? - I need to poop.
(Palm Oil Family members were always together.)
It has been a while.
(They ate the same way.)
(They had the same taste in food.)
(The three had the same passion for dancing.)
(Thus, Palm Oil Family's journey piled up.)
Jang Woo!
Live well.
(They laughed whenever their eyes met.)
The legendary green padded jacket.
(When they were together, they had childhood innocence.)
(And Kian84)
That's right. The zipper.
(They could share anything.)
I can only put it on the left side.
I remember that.
(And the Rainbow Club family)
Jang Woo! Hye Won! Live happily!
Congratulations.
Come on!
Heave-ho!
(For 6 years, they spend time together...)
- Be happy. - Congratulations.
(and became precious to each other.)
- It's time for the photo. - The photo with the officiant.
Please stand in the middle.
- I can't believe I officiated it. - Thank you, Hyun Moo.
Right. They take a separate photo with the officiant.
- Yes. They take a separate photo. - I see.
Yes. You always see that photo in your parents' wedding album.
One, two.
The officiant always wears the aviator glasses.
That's right.
I'm the officiant.
(A photo with the officiant)
(They take a photo with the host.)
(Hyun Moo debuted as an officiant.)
(Kian84 debuted as a host.)
(They plucked up their courage for Jang Woo.)
Thank you.
- Congratulations. - Enjoy the food.
- We'll go and say hello soon. - Okay.
- Jang Woo, see you soon. - Jang Woo put...
a lot of care into the food.
- It was tasty. - It was really tasty.
- He didn't disappoint. - Jang Woo didn't disappoint.
Groom and bride don't even have time to eat.
At what age do you want to get married?
I got 4 readings in the 4 Pillars of Destiny.
They told me to get married at the age of 35 or 36.
So I want to get married in five years.
That's the plan.
At the age of 35?
Why?
(Shaking his head)
- Don't believe in such things. - Did you get married at that age?
At what age do you want to get married?
I don't want to get married.
Have you always wanted to stay celibate?
- I think I'm a bit like that. - I see.
- Really? - He's a celibate.
I never feel jealous when I watch people's weddings.
If I feel jealous,
- Right. - I'll want to get married.
But I never think, "I want to get married someday."
What's under the gochujang sole?
It's saffron risotto.
Saffron risotto.
That dish was tasty.
It's like a dish...
a foreign chef has made...
- for Koreans. - That's right.
(She takes a bite of the steak.)
- The steak was nice and tender. - It was tender.
(Eating)
The abalone is tasty.
It's so tasty.
- They're here. - They're here.
The reception. Their outfits are so pretty.
- He looks cool. - They're pretty.
- I was so thankful... - Congratulations.
since he came to our table as soon as the reception began.
- I know. - I was so thankful.
Why did you wear white?
- What? - Where did you get the courage?
What?
- It's my wedding. - You're like mashed potato.
- Jang Woo seemed like an adult. - Thank you for coming.
He's an adult.
- Today is Jang Woo's last day. - You're right.
He'll graduate from I Live Alone.
- Congratulations. - We'll live well.
- Thank you. - Congratulations.
Live well.
(The Rainbow Club members congratulate him sincerely.)
- Thank you. - Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - Mr. Groom.
- I'll get going now. - Okay.
- I'll get going now. - See you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow. I'll get going now.
I'll get going now, Kang Yong.
- Well done, Hyun Moo. - That's right. Well done.
Congratulations on your perfect debut as a host.
I'll get going now.
Thank you for your hard work.
(The officiant leaves the wedding venue.)
When you tuned around and headed out,
you looked so forlorn.
You looked so lonely.
I'm tired.
- Look at him. - Oh, no.
I don't think I can watch this.
What? Why do I look so depressed?
He brought flowers.
(Haggard)
Did he come back so late?
The wedding began at 6pm.
- My goodness. - My goodness.
My goodness.
It's so quiet.
It was already on the internet...
because everyone had filmed it.
(Fidgeting)
(Like)
Do you know the person who posted it?
No.
I was tagged.
(The short-form videos he's in)
(Like)
He likes everything.
He likes all the posts about him.
(He regains energy by looking at himself on social media.)
(Hmph)
(Getting up)
(He puts the flowers from the wedding in a vase.)
I'm so exhausted.
My energy is drained.
(He comes back to the sofa with flowers.)
It's nice that there are flowers.
I know. They're nice to look at.
- Is that the wedding message? - Yes. It's what he wrote earlier.
(He unfolds the wedding message and pressed it with a book.)
- No way. - Will he take a photo?
(He takes a photo to show that he has officiated a wedding.)
I wondered why he brought back the flowers.
The new groom.
- Hyun Moo. - What? Are you home already?
No. We cleaned up...
and came back to the waiting room.
Thank you so much, Hyun Moo.
Don't mention it. You gave me a good opportunity.
When you looked at me earlier,
I was moved.
- Right? - I had planned...
to deliver the message...
- Okay. - while looking at you guys.
But your eyes became a bit moist.
He was right.
(Moist)
So I looked at the space between you and Hye Won...
to avoid meeting your eye.
Right.
It was so touching. Thank you.
We'll live well, Hyun Moo.
Okay, Jang Woo.
You must have many people to call. You should hang up now.
Okay, Hyun Moo. Thank you.
Okay.
My goodness.
- My goodness. - My goodness.
Why is everyone sighing?
It isn't like that.
How did you feel?
I was jealous.
- Really? - I was jealous of Jang Woo.
Usually, when I host a wedding,
I never think, "I feel lonely."
"I want to be like them."
But they looked so happy.
I felt jealous for the first time in a long while...
after the wedding.
I'm a bit hungry.
Will you eat ramyeon?
Of course.
A steak wasn't enough to fill me up.
(Adding the seasoning)
In the Han River ramyeon style, I kept the lid open.
Live happily.
(Sniffing)
What are those?
Those are wild-harvested pine mushrooms.
My goodness.
I always put them in ramyeon.
- Pine mushrooms in ramyeon? - What a waste.
Do you put them in ramyeon?
I don't have time to cook.
How precious.
Are they different from the mushroom you get at a barbecue place?
- They're totally different. - They're totally different.
- They're very expensive. - They're very expensive.
I see.
It's tasty.
(Is it cooked?)
It looks tasty.
With kimchi...
(He adds kimchi and Woo Il's dried laver.)
- Woo Il's dried laver. - It's tasty.
It's tasty.
I'll add more saltiness to salty food.
(Stirring)
(Slurping)
Do you eat standing up?
I eat standing up these days.
(He puts a piece of kimchi on the top.)
(He inhales the food hurriedly.)
That and Woo Il's dried laver.
The dried laver is very tasty.
- That's right. It's tasty. - The dried laver is tasty.
(Crunchy)
I love...
eating salty food with salty food.
It's a salty meal.
Why is ramyeon so tasty?
(He fills his body with sodium.)
My goodness. Oh, no.
- Oh, no. - He choked on his food.
(Hyun Moo)
- My goodness. - I thought he was eating hurriedly.
He should've sat down.
It's gone already.
(He slurps the noodles as he remains standing up.)
Even after a full-course meal at the wedding venue,
I had room for ramyeon.
(He drinks the soup from the pot.)
It had the pine mushroom aroma.
I forgot to add them!
- What? - Gosh!
What was I thinking?
You forgot to add the pine mushrooms.
I forgot to add the pine mushrooms.
- What? - The pine mushroom aroma?
You said it had the pine mushroom aroma.
It had the pine mushroom aroma.
You can just dip them in sesame oil.
(He used pine mushrooms as a diffuser.)
What was I thinking?
(He finally has ramyeon with pine mushrooms.)
- It looks tasty. - I'm going crazy.
It doesn't get more luxurious than that.
It looks so tasty.
Perfect.
If I don't eat pine mushrooms like that, they'll go bad.
- That's right. - That's right.
- It's better to eat them. - I have to eat them like that.
(He eats ramyeon with wild-harvested pine mushrooms.)
I made a hot debut as an officiant.
As for officiating...
I want to officiate my own wedding.
- What? - What?
Moomoo, you haven't gotten married once.
You aren't even divorced. You haven't gotten married once.
Just like running,
you're good at officiating,
Moomoo.
(I'm proud of myself.)
I don't know what I'm feeling.
You should add "Moo" to officiating.
- Call it Mooficiating. - Mooficiating.
- Moomoo's Mooficiating. - Yes.
I'm hungry.
- Ramyeon. - Ramyeon is the best.
- I'll eat ramyeon today. - It's the tastiest.
I'm craving ramyeon.
(Ask Moomoo to Mooficiate Your Wedding)
If I get married, I'll ask Kian84 to host it.
It was nice.
It was much better than my cliched way of doing it.
- It was unpredictable. - Right?
He didn't cross the line.
- It was unpredictable. - It was so nice.
- Well... - Right? He didn't cross the line.
I'll be able to do it, right?
- Why do you say that? - Gosh.
- Don't be like that. - I'll be able to host it, right?
- Well... - Don't be too realistic.
Will you say yes if someone asks you to officiate their wedding?
People who like being bored...
People who like being bored can ask me anytime.
(Clicking)
What?
- What? - That startled me.
(Their eyes go wide.)
(Opening)
(Jang Woo makes a surprise visit.)
- That startled me. - What? This is so sudden.
Welcome.
- Congratulations again, new groom. - Thank you.
Congratulations.
I'm happy to see him.
- I felt bad that I couldn't go. - That's right. KEY couldn't come.
I felt the need to say my last goodbye.
- My goodness. - My goodness.
This is your last day...
- on I Live Alone. - Yes.
- Please say what you want. - It feels strange.
I spent my 30s...
(Looking back)
with the Rainbow Club members.
I lived the days anyone would be jealous of.
- Welcome. - Hello.
(From 2019,)
(he spent 6 years...)
(on I Live Alone.)
(A rainbow rose in his 30s thanks to that.)
It still doesn't feel real.
So I don't know how to define this feeling.
Thank you so much...
for being by my side during my 30s and filling my days with happiness.
I'll live well for anyone to see.
- Okay. - Thank you.
My goodness.
You spent your 30s here,
but I spent my 30s and 40s here.
So there will be someone when you go home, right?
- How does that feel? - My house is very warm.
- There's warmth. - My goodness.
No matter how much we turn on the heater, the house remains cold.
You know what I mean, right?
There's only so much a heater can do.
A person's warmth heats up the house differently.
That's right.
I actually knew about Jang Woo's visit.
I prepared something as the president of Rainbow Club.
- What? - I'll bring it.
- You should've... - Kian84, help me.
- discussed it with us. - No.
- What is it? - What?
- What? My goodness. - What is it?
- What? - What is it?
Firstly, there's an item in Jangwoo Green.
On top of Jangwoo Green,
I'll put an appreciation plaque.
(Here's an appreciation plaque.)
Please hold it.
- It's so pretty. - It contains our love.
"Appreciation plaque for Club Member Lee Jang Woo."
"As he has appeared on the show as Chef Powder in 2019..."
"and filled up many people's Friday..."
"with a lot of energy,"
"we give this plaque."
"From the Rainbow Club members of I Live Alone."
- There's one more thing. - How cute!
- Congratulations on your wedding - Congratulations on your wedding
(He opens a banner.)
- Congratulations, dear Jang Woo - Congratulations, dear Jang Woo
(Congratulations on your wedding.)
Congratulations on your wedding.
Thank you so much.
Live well. Pay back by living well.
- We'll live well. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - It's nice.
Dowoon,
- it has been a while. - It has been a while.
What have you been up to?
I've practiced...
- and prepared for a concert. - You've fished as well.
You were my seafood brother.
- That's right. - You promised to call...
if you caught anything.
(Dowoon had so much love for fishing.)
(Leave seafood to me.)
(Seafood brother promised to share sashimi.)
Haven't you caught anything?
I haven't caught anything yet.
If you send me a direct message...
- A direct message? - A direct message?
The sea is full of tasty fishes these days.
Yellowtail is in season.
- Yellowtail. - Yellowtail tastes good now.
- I'll need to go on a trip. - You're my seafood brother.
Okay.
(Rest for a Beat)
(Dowoon is holding something.)
The house looks different during the day.
I think the house became a bit brighter.
- It's because it's during the day. - It's because it's during the day.
- It's because it's during the day. - We're used to seeing it at night.
(The kitchen looks brighter during the day.)
His fridge looks the same.
- Wasn't it there back then? Cake. - Cake.
(Inside the empty fridge...)
What?
(was a cake.)
(He couldn't fill the fridge due to his busy schedule.)
It's a cake my bandmate has made for me.
He'll complain if I throw it away.
(He couldn't throw away the cake.)
He's finally filling up the fridge.
It's my first time seeing the walls of the fridge.
(Full)
I spend more time at home these days.
I decided to use this opportunity to fill up the fridge...
and went to a grocery store.
There are times...
when I feel a bit hungry and think, "I don't want to order anything."
At those times, it'll be nice to eat frozen food.
It'll be a special treat.
I checked the expiration dates.
It's so nice that they're good for years.
It's fun to fill the empty fridge.
When will my fridge get empty like that?
(Hesitant)
(Beeping)
(Halting)
(Pressing)
- He hasn't done it before. - He's using it for the first time.
It's tricky at first.
How does it work?
- It's locked at first. - That's right.
I used the induction stove for the first time since moving.
My schedule was packed. I was so busy.
I was using it after six months.
It's tricky.
He must've been busy. There's nothing at home.
(He takes out hot sauce and frozen pork belly slices.)
(He pours frozen pork belly slices to the pan.)
I know what he's going to make.
- What's that? - What's that?
- It's a typical dish... - I recognize it.
for people who can't cook.
You know the hotel breakfast, right?
- That's right. - That's what it is, right?
- What? - The hotel breakfast?
- American breakfast. - What?
American breakfast?
To make that, you should've cooked...
- the pork belly slices 1st. - You should've done that 1st.
- That's right. - Otherwise,
the gamey smell goes to the egg.
If he were someone on that level who could make such calculations,
- he wouldn't have made that. - No.
It's the first time I recognized a dish before anyone.
- Thank you so much. - I had no idea what it was.
(He makes something like a hotel breakfast.)
The first meal of the day is...
something I ate often in my previous house.
- It's the K-American breakfast. - That's right.
Pork belly slices and pseudo-scrambled eggs.
A lot of eggshell pieces must've gone in.
That's right.
(Picking out)
(Laughing)
He's laughing.
Seriously, what's this?
- This isn't what I imagined. - I'm a bit better at cooking.
It didn't look as appetizing as I had imagined.
(K-American breakfast is different than what he imagined.)
Gosh, it's hot!
- Gosh, it's hot! - The heat is too high.
Lower the heat.
(Smoke fills up the house, but he remains calm.)
I like burning my food a bit.
It looks like something I'd like.
- I'll make it for you next time. - It's okay.
In most cases, Kian84 doesn't say no.
Kian84 makes something like that and freezes it.
- That's right. - What?
He freezes warm meals...
and eats frozen food.
He's Elsa of the cooking scene.
That's why I don't need to buy frozen food.
I buy fresh food and freeze it.
(Smoky)
(Carefree)
Oh, my.
(My goodness)
He should've turned on the light from the start.
He hadn't turned it on before.
(I see.)
That's right.
- It looks appetizing, right? - It looks nice.
- It looks pretty nice. - Yes.
- As it burned. - Right.
(This should be enough.)
I think it will be okay with some salt and pepper.
(He takes out the instant rice that he heated up.)
Look at how dirty it became.
That's why I don't cook.
Same here.
(He shakes out the hot sauce as well.)
You're going to have it with some hot sauce?
Yes.
He bought it because he was American.
K-American.
(All right.)
(Let's try my K-American breakfast.)
- Gosh, that's hot! - What's wrong?
- You grabbed the hot part, right? - Be careful.
- Right. - Gosh!
What?
(He grabbed the part that was heated up.)
I grabbed it without putting any thought to it.
You're showing all of your charms.
Is that so?
- He has a lot of clumsy charms. - What a man.
Nice.
(Let's calm down.)
(He picks up a lot of the meat first.)
(He dips it in the hot sauce.)
(Eating it in one bite)
These things taste good.
I'm sure that's not what's good.
His standards of taste are low.
- What are you trying to say? - For example, you two...
have experienced many different kinds of good food.
- But as for him... - No. I like good food as well.
To be honest,
it's hard to enjoy...
really good food at home.
It looks awful.
You two failed to connect this time.
(He suddenly gets up.)
That's a really nice cup.
- Why is it nice? - It's huge. I can drink all day.
- It's definitely big. - It's huge!
What is that? Isn't that a beer glass?
Gosh, it's big.
It was good though. I enjoyed it.
It was just like...
a K-American breakfast.
It was salty...
(It was decently salty...)
and spicy.
(and spicy.)
It tasted just right.
I enjoyed it.
That's all that matters.
You're eating it well.
There's not a single tuna can or dried laver packet for a side dish.
(Empty)
It means he was satisfied with what he had.
Right. I just eat what I have.
(He scrapes the leftover rice.)
(Clear)
- Gosh, I like that. - That's neat.
- Clearing up everything. - Right.
(Picking up)
(The used dishes head straight to the sink.)
(Wiping)
(He wipes the table right away as well.)
(Scrubbing hard)
It's because the house is white all around.
- Right. - Right.
(He cleans the induction stove neatly as well.)
(Picking up)
(I will make sure to clean up everything.)
Well,
I'm not that much of a neat freak,
but I remember what my house originally looked like.
As the house was originally neat,
I want to keep it that way even after eating.
(He cleans up right away.)
(Wiping)
I got rid of the grease.
(He washes the dishes next.)
(Tapping)
What's going on?
(He cleans up the food waste neatly as well.)
(Spraying)
What's that?
(He even cleans the sink with the handwash.)
- I do that once in a while. - Once in a while?
- Gosh, I can't believe him. - He's so neat.
Leaving that place dirty attracts roaches, doesn't it?
That area usually doesn't get roaches.
(He finishes up.)
(Gulping)
(Feeling refreshed)
(The kitchen has been restored.)
That's neat.
(Neat)
(He picks up his bag.)
(Walking out)
(Dowoon heads out.)
Where are you going?
(Whistling)
The weather is great too.
(He enters a building.)
It must be the gym or his original home.
Original home?
(He enters an unknown place.)
(He walks in naturally.)
- What? - What?
The drummer.
It's the band master's home.
It's also my practice room and studio.
I was told that there was an empty room,
so I asked to use it while paying for the monthly rent.
He said that was fine.
I've been gratefully using it up until now.
It's set up nicely.
There are times when recordings are done there.
Other people use it as well.
(There are other rooms as well.)
- Do you go often? - Yes. I go really often.
Around 4 to 5 times a week.
(He drops his bag naturally.)
(Shall I start practicing?)
Drummers are so impressive.
How do you play with slippers on?
I love those slippers.
The sole is really thin.
It's easier to hit the drum pedal with thin soles.
Do you need to feel the pedal more?
Do they not come off while playing?
They don't come off easily.
(He's ready with his favorite slippers.)
(Reaching out)
- What's that? - The metronome.
The metronome?
- The tempo is kept with that? - Yes.
(Shall I begin?)
(Splitting up the beat with the metronome)
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- That must be the basics. - Right.
That must be done as a warmup.
What's going on?
Who was that?
What?
What's going on?
- Is it his friend? - Is it the owner of the house?
What?
(Who is that?)
(Someone naturally came into the practice room.)
(Staring)
- It's high, isn't it? - It's really high.
It's a completely different sound from when we perform.
- Right? - It's way too high.
Let's loosen it up then.
(The drum suddenly gets loosened up.)
- What? - Gosh.
- All right. - How low must it be?
It's still high.
The guy who just came in...
is the drummer of Sister's Barbershop, Jeon Dae Jeong.
Oh, Sister's Barbershop?
(Sister's Barbershop made its debut in 1996.)
(The root of Korea's modern rock)
He's from our generation.
He's a senior I rely on a lot and am very grateful for.
Whenever we hold concerts,
he helps out with the drums as the technician.
Drum tuning is really difficult.
- Drums are tuned as well? - Yes.
Drum tuning is really complicated.
- It seems like so. - You'll see why.
- Really? - That's fascinating.
I wanted to learn from him.
I was the host of a band audition.
People like him came out for each band...
and kept working on the drums.
The drums were tightened up and loosened up constantly.
Right. That's done for 20 to 30 minutes.
(A technician is essential for the drums for a performance.)
I've never thought that drums needed to be tuned.
I thought the drum was completely replaced...
if it sounded bad.
- Just as a whole. - No.
Do all of the drums have to be tuned after a four-hour performance?
He would come early the next day...
- and give them a check. - I see.
Do the drums loosen up after a performance?
- Yes. They loosen up. - I suppose so.
They get tuned again for another performance?
(The technician is essential for performances.)
- Do they sound different? - Yes.
It could be because of the skin.
- The skin is a bit weird. - Right.
The skin is quite old.
- What's the skin? - The drum skin.
- It's the top part of the drum. - Right.
- Is that one in better condition? - This one is in good condition.
- Really? - The skin is replaced as well?
Let's see.
That's fascinating.
(Hold on.)
(It's filled with drum tuning tools.)
(The tools get taken out in earnest.)
Here.
I worked on this in the practice room for four hours.
- I just couldn't deal with it. - Four hours?
I tightened it up and loosened it up for four hours.
I gave up in the end.
(The bolts are loosened with a special drill.)
So that's how it's done?
So that comes off.
Pass it to me.
(The old drum skin finally gets removed.)
The first one that was tuned was the snare.
It's the one that gets played a lot.
- The snare. - Drumming is really hard.
Like that?
(The new drum skin is placed on the snare.)
There.
This goes on top.
(The loosened up bolts must be tightened again.)
Screw them on.
(Using his hands to turn them)
All the way until the end.
- Only by hand, right? - Right.
The one that's being turned...
- shouldn't be too tight. - Right.
They should be tightened gently.
- Right. - They aren't fastened tightly.
They can't be dealt with recklessly.
- Just so that they don't turn. - Right.
- This much. - They don't turn, right?
They're secured first.
Other instruments use a tuner to get tuned.
So that's completely different from tuning other instruments.
Go around and check if the sounds are the same.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
(Tapping)
- What do you think? - It's higher.
Right. That's when you lower it.
Is it this one or this one?
I'll go with this one.
So...
So the balance is important as well.
- What do you think? - That's fascinating.
It's nice.
Gosh, those of us who don't play are clueless.
It all sounds the same.
(He checks the snare that has been tuned.)
It's nice.
(The tuning is done with his talented hands.)
Good.
(The pitch has been brought down after getting tuned.)
- Right. - Right.
Give it a try and loosen this one up as well.
- Should I try with this one? - Sure.
This one is really hard to tune.
He can't stay by my side forever.
I should learn how to tune the drums myself...
as I might happen to perform on my own.
I heard there was a specific sound of each drum.
- Right. - Right.
(Burning with passion)
I'll try to remember the exact sound...
and tune it just the same way.
- Really? - Yes.
It's a special private lesson.
Right. This is really hard.
This is something you can't learn elsewhere.
(He confidently loosens up the bolts first.)
All right.
(Reaching out)
- Don't touch it. It's mine. - Oh, is that so?
(I'll do it on my own.)
Shall I begin?
It will definitely sound dry right now.
- That's the first step done. - Be bold.
Be bold. Don't back down.
- Screw it tight. - Right.
This feels like a prison escape.
(Serious)
(He screws the bolt boldly.)
(Ringing)
Gosh.
- There's a bit of ringing. - It sounds low.
It sounds off.
(Ringing)
(Clear)
It does sound strange even to us who don't know much.
- It's a bit different. - It sounds off even to us.
It doesn't sound pretty when you hear it.
- It doesn't sound pretty. - No.
(Crying)
I should loosen it up again.
You have to do this 10,000 times to get a better sound.
He has to do it 10,000 times?
That must be how he trained himself.
This is really hard.
So the tuning makes a big difference.
I think it's even harder because it's done just by ear.
Try to fix the sound.
It doesn't sound nice.
- Right. - Try to fix it.
What will he do to fix it?
- Will he get it fixed right away? - I'm curious.
(Tapping carefully)
It was ringing up there.
He's like a human cultural asset.
So that's how it's done.
(He tightens the bolts without hesitation.)
That's why a professional is different.
He finds the right balance and fixes the lacking parts.
- Right. - That's how it's done.
(Amazed)
That will be too hard to do.
I think I'm done with it.
(Clear)
- It sounds different. - It sounds different.
I think it sounds nice.
- Gosh, that's fascinating. - Gosh.
(Let's work on the other drums.)
I think it will take a lot of time...
for me to do it on my own.
That sounds nice.
(He works on the other drums in a flash as well.)
They sound nice.
- I'll get going. - Okay.
- Bye. - Bye.
You must feel grateful for him.
- Definitely. - Gosh.
The expert.
- I won't see you out. - All right.
Thank you!
(He sits back down as the tuning is over.)
(It sounds nice.)
There he goes again.
(Going around the drums)
(He focuses on the beat with his eyes closed.)
(He repeats the same beat over and over.)
It's just like "Whiplash."
(He starts sweating like crazy.)
(For over an hour,)
(he practices the same part.)
That must prevent you from gaining weight.
You sweat like crazy when drumming, as if it's a marathon.
- You surely must have stamina. - Right.
I've watched his performance.
He kept playing with the same energy for two hours and a half.
Right.
We love our fans when we perform,
so we decide to give it our all for them.
It must hurt after you're done.
- I pass out after it's over. - You pass out?
- I come home and pass out. - Right.
I feel totally exhausted.
His stamina is phenomenal.
(For performances over two hours and a half,)
(he regularly works on the basics.)
- Gosh. - How is that even done?
My forearms hurt just by watching.
(Practicing endlessly)
(Crash)
(He sat down and practiced for two hours.)
Gosh, that's amazing.
He won't need to do a separate workout.
That's a full-body workout.
- Did he wet his pants? - I think so.
I definitely wet my pants.
Whenever I perform,
there's always a circle on my bottom.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
Look at this sweat.
The fans might make fun of you.
But that can't be helped.
Is that why rockers wear black leather pants?
- That must be why. - Right.
It won't show with those pants.
Gosh, I should stop now.
(He sweated buckets during practice.)
Gosh, I just did a workout.
(Trudging out)
(His two-hour drum practice comes to an end.)
Gosh, that was a long practice.
Okay.
(He heads somewhere while it's dark outside.)
(He got changed as well as he sweated.)
(Itaewon Station)
Itaewon?
(He walks while looking ahead.)
(Peeking)
(Dowoon heads into a building.)
He must be getting an eyebrow tattoo.
He's getting an eyebrow tattoo?
So many men get them these days.
- Really? - Me?
- I got an eyebrow tattoo as well. - Really?
- Yes. - Really?
- Bring up your hair for us. - Let's see it briefly.
- I really got an eyebrow tattoo. - It turned out really nice!
Were you always like Mona Lisa?
You did well to get the eyebrow tattoo.
It looks really natural.
It looks nice and natural.
It says, "Beauty Academy."
- Right. - So that was why you said that.
Where is this?
It's this red?
What is this place?
(Dowoon heads in somewhere.)
Where is this?
It's this red?
What is this place?
(The music gets louder as he gets closer.)
I made a reservation as Yoon Do Woon.
Oh, right. This way, please.
It's a live bar?
Gosh, it reminds me of "La La Land."
(A jazz bar in Itaewon)
- There was a place like this? - That's nice.
It's a place where I can freely talk to my friend...
while listening to a live performance.
I've always...
admired clubs with live performances.
- That's the vibe you get abroad. - A jazz bar.
When I see great drummers or other performers,
it impresses me a lot.
- Is it called catharcism? - "Catharcism?"
That is what I feel there.
I've always dreamt of becoming someone...
who makes others feel that way since a young age.
I think that was why I went to live clubs often.
(Eyes fixed)
(The performance has been going on for a while in the jazz bar.)
(Watching intently)
Is that Kim Hyun Chul?
Gosh, that's so impressive.
(That was great.)
They're so impressive.
(He focuses on the music as if he was possessed.)
Here you are.
What?
- Who are they? - They must be his friends.
He has a guitar on his back.
I'll sit there.
Choose your drinks.
- When did you get here? - What?
It has been a while.
Both of them were my seniors in the army.
One of them is a percussionist for MeloMance.
His name is Jung Sol.
What is a percussionist?
When the drummer plays the regular beat,
the percussionist plays the rhythms in between.
- He's an amazing percussionist. - Really?
The other guy is a guitarist who works really hard. Won Seok.
He's an amazing guitarist!
Right. He's great.
(The talented guitarist who reached the final...)
(of "University Song Festival" that Hyun Moo hosted)
Awesome.
It's been a while to see this uniform.
We contact each other often even after getting discharged.
- What did you do before this? - I practiced.
(I practiced.)
Are you busy these days?
These days? I have a lot more time now.
Are there no concerts for MeloMance?
This year's tour for MeloMance is over.
Really? What are you up to these days?
I've been working out.
I'm planning to start boxing starting from tomorrow.
- Really? - Yes.
(The place is filled with people who want to rest with music.)
That's great.
(Impressed)
He's a bit like Yoon Sang.
(He's focused at one spot.)
The drummer is my professor at school.
- Who? - He's a professor.
Really?
(The professor who drums)
They're all talented musicians.
(The talented musicians have gathered at the jazz bar.)
(Flipping)
Why is one stick flipped around?
- Did he make a mistake? - When the rim is hit,
it sounds even better when hit with the thicker part of the stick.
What is the rim?
- The rim. - The edge of the drum.
It's the edge of the drum. When that part is hit,
- it makes a tapping sound. - I see.
The sound of the rim.
(The professor plays rim shots.)
Gosh, it sounds so pretty.
(Eyes shining brightly)
(Fancy)
(Amazed)
There's a jam session starting from Part Two.
Take a picture of the QR code...
and make your request...
- A jam session? - via Google Form.
It's called Jam Day for impromptu performances.
So the people there can come out and perform?
- Right. - I see.
People who want to perform make their requests...
and they perform together.
(Going up while being in the audience)
- That's impressive. - I love that vibe.
Right!
(They all take turns to perform on the spot.)
- So if Kian84 makes a request, - Yes?
can he sing with them?
Right.
I want to do a jazz performance.
Hyun Moo!
- I want to perform now as well! - Right?
Just like that out of nowhere?
How can you just say you want to do a jazz performance?
He's going to start something while calling him Moosician.
Gosh, "Moosician!"
- "Jazz Moosician." - Oh, gosh!
I remember you failing as Moosician once.
- Right! - Really?
His attempt to become Moozart was a total failure!
Moozart was a total failure.
I learned to play the piano while trying to become Moozart...
and I gave up as it took so long.
Gosh, I just put that up for sale on the flea market.
I didn't even use it once!
- Put it up for sale. - It's completely new.
- Gosh, Moozart. - Right.
- I should put that up for sale. - I should buy that.
(He takes out his phone to participate.)
Gosh, that's impressive. I love these vibes!
Will you be able to do this?
Out of the people who are here, we will begin...
with the ones who are on top of the list.
Park Tae Seo on the drums.
(The first person to make the request)
Gosh, that's so impressive!
Musicians are so cool.
That must be exciting.
Gosh, that's amazing.
- They must be students. - Right.
There are many talented musicians.
(The performance begins right away.)
They're starting right away?
How is it possible to start right away?
- So they're strangers performing. - Right.
Without even playing together once.
Right. They only discuss what song to play.
(Watching the performance in awe)
(Dowoon learns jazz once again today while enjoying the performance.)
(Fancy piano skills)
This is the thing I'm most curious about.
How do they come up with the ending?
They haven't worked together.
They all check each other.
- Right. - They're all checking each other.
- They do this. - They check their faces.
- They exchange looks. - They're checking each other.
Like that.
(Ending naturally)
(A big round of applause)
- You guys are up next. - Lee Won Seok...
and Jung Sol. Please come up to the stage.
(You guys are up!)
(Excited)
(Jung Sol plays the bongos.)
The bongos!
- I know that one. - Percussion.
Electric guitar.
(They all get up on stage with their instruments.)
Actually, our drummer today...
is Mr. Kim Hong Ki of Seoul Institute of the Arts.
- Gosh, he's impressive. - The one right here...
who is the guitarist is his student.
- The two will perform together. - Gosh, that's awesome!
(He is excited about his friends' performance.)
Why aren't you performing, Dowoon?
Oh, right.
To be honest, I know nothing about that genre.
- I see. - I know nothing.
I want to study it and go up in the future.
- It's completely different, right? - Right.
- When it comes to drumming. - Right. Completely different.
I won't be able to sing jazz even when I get asked to.
It's a completely different world.
(I see.)
(Shall we begin?)
(The intro sounds extraordinary.)
(Impressed)
(Tapping)
(The performance begins with the lead of the drums.)
That's so nice!
- Gosh, that's nice. - Gosh, that's nice.
(Dowoon's friends perform skillfully.)
Gosh!
It feels different with the guitar.
(They improvise as they perform.)
(Passionate)
(The performance builds up.)
(Controlling the volume)
(Keeping the rhythm)
(Jung Sol's bongo solo)
Oh, Jung Sol!
(Entranced)
(Screaming)
I thought this to myself as I watched them perform.
They seemed like clumsy guys all the time,
but they felt impressive.
DAY6 is about showing our teamwork on stage.
But this is a place of improvised performances...
and languages and skills of various instruments.
There was a different charm about the performance.
You must have learned a lot.
I did.
(Making eye contact)
(They start playing together again!)
- What's this? - It's a shout-out.
"He just did a solo. Isn't he amazing?"
So this is a shout-out.
Can't you perform in a club if you try?
With just a bit of practice.
- I'll give it a try. - Right.
- He can surely do it. - We should all go and watch.
- Right. - That sounds great.
Thank you.
I think it will be fun to perform with them on stage.
I should come up with a routine to work on the basics.
I want to be able to get into a bit of jazz as well.
I was naturally humbled there.
To me, the drums...
are my friends who always give me the whip...
without much reward.
(The drummer with 10 years of experience...)
(takes another step of growth while watching a different genre.)
(There's No End to the Path of Learning)
(Next episode)
(The world's best professional baseball league)
(2017, Asian Professional Baseball Championship, silver medal)
(2018, 2019, 2020, KBO Golden Glove)
(2019, WBSC Premier 12 Runner-up)
(He made it to Major League afterward.)
(The all-rounder that has everything on the ground)
(First Korean Major League Golden Glove Winner in 2023)
(Hello.)
(I'm Kim Ha Seong, and I'm a baseball player.)
(There's Latin music playing.)
(Where is this place?)
(The view that is seen during off-season)
(The golden awards that represent his hard work)
(Fancy items that suit that Golden Glover)
(They're like gifts that I give to myself.)
(I can't rest even during off-season!)
(Breathing out)
(It's easy.)
(With his golden muscles that aren't easy to make,)
(he's working out easily.)
(He puts on his glove tightly.)
(Shall we begin in earnest?)
I cook when I want something.
(Golden muscles)
(Shaking)
(I'll show you my golden cooking skills as well.)
(The Major Leaguer is a lover of Korean food.)
(Slurping)
(It's so good.)
(What's up?)
(Why are you here again?)
(Kim Ha Seong's Golden Off-Season)
(The kimchi during KEY's housewarming party)
(Mesmerized)
(It's the kimchi of my African American dancer's mother-in-law.)
(African American dancer's mother-in-law gave you kimchi?)
(He went to meet them.)
(His bestie, Dancer Kany)
(Today's kimchi master, Kany's mother-in-law)
(While helping her make kimchi,)
(I'm going to learn her secret of making good kimchi.)
(There are...)
(around 70 cabbages that have to be made.)
(The kimchi master's hard training begins.)
(The best ingredients are collected from the master's field.)
(Mul kimchi)
(Everybody, mul kimchi)
(Endlessly grabbing the ingredients with the kimchi song)
(I'm already exhausted.)
(The kimchi master's secret will save their tired bodies.)
(Amazed)
(A new world of kimjang)
(The pupils are grooving while julienning radishes.)
(In no time, there's a pile of radishes.)
(Staying energetic with the never-ending labor songs)
(With Kany singing, things are moving fast.)
(The secrets of the kimchi master are revealed.)
(Another refill of napa cabbages)
(It's too soon to give up.)
(Until the Last Napa Cabbage)